containerstore.com 2017-12-29

# Privacy Policy | The Container Store

###  By accessing or using The Container Store website, providing information to us through a contact center or at one of our stores, or buying our products, you agree to the terms of the most recent version of this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. 

Last updated on 8/8/2014 

The Container Store does not sell or share your personal information with other companies for their marketing efforts. We pride ourselves on providing exceptional customer service. Not only are we committed to helping you organize your life, we also want to make sure you clearly understand how we use information about you to provide you with the best possible shopping experience. We value the trust you place in The Container Store and we want to ensure that you understand what information we gather about you, how we use it, and the safeguards we have in place to protect it. 

This Privacy Policy applies to information collected by The Container Store through our Internet website (currently located at www.containerstore.com) and our associated mobile sites (collectively our "Site"), our contact centers, including our toll-free number, Customer Solutions email service, or online chat (collectively our "Contact Center"), and our store locations (our "Stores"). It is designed to ensure that our customers understand how and why The Container Store collects and uses the information provided to us. You can learn how to opt out of receiving catalogs, e-mails and other marketing materials from us here. 

The following topics are addressed in this Privacy Policy: 

  * Acceptance of Terms

  * Collecting Personal Information

  * Browsing Our Site

  * How We May Use Your Information

  * Sharing Your Information and Third-party Partnerships

  * Disclosure of Your Personal Information

  * Security of Our Site

  * Reviewing and Revising Your Account Information

  * Opting Out

  * Children and Privacy

  * Information Provided When You Apply for a Job Online

  * Questions

## Acceptance of Terms

By using our Site, our Contact Center, or our Stores, you agree to The Container Store's Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy at any time. If this policy changes in the future, we will let you know by posting the updated policy on our Site with the most recent modification date. Please check this page periodically for changes. If there are material changes in the way we will use or share personal information about you, we will provide notice of our revised Privacy Policy when you access your online account or provide you with an email notification. Your continued use of our Site, our Contact Center, or our Stores following the posting of the revised policy means you accept the changed policy. 

##  Collecting Personal Information 

We collect information about you when you make a purchase in one of our Stores, through our Contact Center, or through our Site. This information may include your name, mailing and billing address, zip code, phone number, and/or email address. We may also ask for this information if you choose to participate in a survey, sweepstakes, contest, promotion or giveaway. We consider information that personally identifies you, such as your name, email address or billing information, and other data that is linked to such information, to be personal information. 

You can browse our Site and read our editorial content without providing any personal information. However, you must provide personal information in order to make a purchase. With sales transactions, we may collect payment information including credit/debit card information, gift card and merchandise credit numbers, and/or checking account information. When you make a purchase in one of our Stores, through our Contact Center, or through our Site, we collect transactional information related to your purchase (i.e., what you bought, the price you paid, the payment method you used, and if the product was on sale). 

We use third-party partners to collect information about your use of our Site and your product preferences. If you have provided us with your personal information, information about your use of our Site and your preferences may be linked to your personal information so that we may more effectively market to you, or to help identify problems on our Site. 

We have software that allows us to re-create your sessions on our Site. We use this information to make our Site easier and more enjoyable to use. If you have provided us with your personal information, information about your use of our Site may be linked to your personal information, and may be used to contact you in order to address problems you may have experienced while using our Site. 

We also collect some personal information when you use other features of our Site. We collect your email address if you sign up for our email list. In order to establish an online account, you will be asked to provide your name, email address, and zip code, and you will also need to establish a password. If you use online chat to connect with our Contact Center, we will ask for your name and email address. We may also permit you to sign on to your online account with The Container Store using log-in information (such as an e-mail address and password) you have established for using a social network profile or account (such as Facebook® or Twitter®). If you choose to do so, those credentials may be communicated to and used by a third party service provider to authenticate your credentials and ensure that access to your account is obtained properly, and to facilitate your use of you social network log-in to access your account with us. In addition, if you are a new customer and want to use your social network log-in to access your account with The Container Store, some information about you (such as your name, e-mail address, and location information) may be automatically delivered to us as part of the process by which you sign up for your account. 

You may be asked to provide additional information when you use our Site to develop personal organization projects, custom space designs, registries, or wish lists. This information may be linked to personal information you have provided, such as your name. In addition, we may provide you with the ability to use social networks to share information about product purchases or interests, registries, wish lists, or other activities in which you engage on the Site. If you choose to share such information, your name and/or other personal information may be linked to the information you share about activities on our Site. 

**You will be asked to provide personal information if you apply for a job with The Container Store using our online application process, as explained in the "Information Provided When You Apply for a Job Online"section below. **

Finally, The Container Store may allow you to submit information to our Ratings & Reviews, our customers' real-life tips and our "What We Stand For" blog (collectively referred to as "Forums"). Your use of the Forums may reveal your user name, city and state, and may allow you to publish certain other personal information about yourself. Information you submit to our Forums, including your user name, and in some cases, your city and state, becomes publicly available and can be seen, collected, and used by others. Once made public, this information cannot be made private again. Therefore, you should exercise caution when deciding to submit information to our Forums, or disclosing information about yourself or others, and you should not submit or communicate any information to the Forums that you do not want to be seen, collected, or used by others. We may link information you submit to our Forums to other information about you, including but not limited to your personal information and account information, but we will not publicly display your personal or account information other than as explained above. 

##  Browsing Our Website 

When you are using our Site, we log your **IP address** (a number that identifies your computer on the Internet) for system administration, troubleshooting and to examine overall traffic trends. For example, IP addresses help us determine the percentage of people coming from various online gateways, such as Google or Yahoo!. This information is collected in aggregate. It is also linked to your personal information if you provide your personal information to The Container Store. 

Another tool we use is called a **cookie** , which is a small data file stored on your computer that allows us to customize portions of our Site to your preferences. Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our product selection to you, and to ensure that only you have access to your account and any personal organization projects, wish lists or custom space designs you have created with us. The cookie, by itself, doesn't provide any personal information, such as your name or email address. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) However, you may not be able to use some features of our Site if you set your browser to reject cookies. 

We have implemented Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting on our Site, which provides us with information about categories of users who visit our site, such as the number of men and women, our visitors' age ranges, and our visitors' general interests. Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting does not provide us with any personal information about you, such as your name or email address. We use information from Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to help us to better understand our customers and potential customers.   
Google permits you to opt-out of some of their services by using [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). For example, visitors can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads. Google provides additional information about Google Analytics and additional opt-out options [here](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) and [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

We also use cookies and other tools to collect information about how you use our Site (for example, information about what pages you look at, what terms you use in searching our Site, or what products you investigate or purchase). This information may be collected directly by us, or it may be collected by a third-party service provider. If you have an account with us, this information may be linked to your account in order to provide you with product recommendations. 

Please know that while some browsers allow you to send a signal indicating that you do not wish to be "tracked", our Site does not recognize or respond to these "Do Not Track" signals. 

##  How We May Use Your Information 

In order to serve you better, we may combine the information you provide us and the information we have from your purchases through our Site, through our Contact Center, online and in our Stores. We may also utilize information that is publicly available. This information, in total, is used to improve your overall experience with our company. Here are the ways we may use information about you in order to enhance your shopping experience at The Container Store: 

  * **To complete your purchases**. We use information about your transactions, including personal information you have provided, in order to process payments you have made and deliver products you have ordered. In doing so, we may transmit payment information to third parties, such as banks, credit card companies or payment clearance services. We may also provide shipping information to third parties in order to permit them to deliver products to you.   

  * **For marketing and promotional purposes**. We send targeted direct mail and catalogs to our customers about products or events that we think may be of interest, based on past purchases at The Container Store. We may also send offers for discounts or promotions and information about campaigns, new products or new features. In addition, we send email communications to let customers know about promotions, organizational tips, and the most up-to-date happenings at The Container Store. However, you can opt out of receiving catalogs, e-mails and other marketing materials from us. Information on how to opt out is provided below.   

  * **To improve the content and navigation on our Site**. For example, we may use cookies or other tools to track which sections or products online are most often visited and in what order.   

  * **To enhance your online shopping experience**. For example, we may use information about you to recognize you and welcome you back to our Site, personalizing your shopping experience, or to place advertisements or links on this Site for goods and services likely to be of interest to you.   

  * **To make your use of our Site compatible with the social networks you use**. For example, we and/or service providers we use may use your personal information to make it possible for you to access your account with The Container Store using the log-in information you use for your social network account, or in connection with allowing you to share information about your activities on our Site through your social networks. 

##  Sharing Your Information and Third-party Partnerships 

As previously stated, we do not sell or share your personal information with other companies for their marketing efforts. On occasion, The Container Store shares information collected from our customers with selected third-party companies who help assist us in our own advertising and marketing efforts. For example, we may retain an outside company to help us with customer research or to manage a customer database, to send catalogs or direct mail, or to send email messages. The information we provide to third parties for such purposes may include your name, address, email address, Site usage, and purchase information, which will help us target marketing communications. The Container Store also provides some anonymous information about customer purchases to third-party companies that assist us with advertising and promoting our products and services. 

You can opt out of receiving catalogs, e-mails and other marketing materials from us. Information on how to opt out is provided below. 

We participate in special partnerships with other companies that we believe offer products or services that our customers would be interested in and would benefit from. We do not share customers' personal information with these partner companies. Customers may receive information about these partnerships and related promotions directly from The Container Store or from the third-party companies that assist us with marketing. 

The Container Store may also enter into a "co-branding" relationship with another company, or organization. At times, we may communicate with customers on behalf of that company and customers may be directed to a partner website to purchase a specific item or learn about their services. In these cases, both The Container Store and the partner company may receive personal information you provide. 

Additionally, like many other companies, The Container Store may use outside marketing companies to place advertisements or links on other websites. When you visit this Site, these companies may collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., your IP address, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) about your visits to this Site and your visits to other websites over time in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information about your online activities over time and across different web sites. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising by certain participating advertising networks, you can visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> and [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) In addition, Google permits you to opt-out of some of their services by using [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads), and provides information and additional opt-out options for Google Analytics [here](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) and [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). The Container Store is not responsible for the collection or use of information by such marketing companies or third-party websites. 

Third parties may receive your personal information because you have visited their websites or accessed their links. Please refer to their privacy policies to learn about how they handle your personal information. Please note that The Container Store has no control over the privacy practices of other companies of websites, and we do not assume any responsibility or liability for any third-party's data collection or disclosure practices, their failure to abide by their privacy policies, or the content of their websites. 

In the event that The Container Store is merged with or acquired by another company, or in the event of a transfer of our assets, we may disclose or transfer personal information and other information about usage of our Site in connection with such a transaction. In the event of such a transfer, we will notify you of the change of control of your personal information. You should also be aware that courts may have the authority under certain circumstances to permit personal information and other information about usage of our Site to be shared or transferred to third parties without your permission. 

##  Disclosure of Your Personal Information 

We will not use or disclose your personal information except: (1) as described in this Privacy Policy; (2) after obtaining your permission to a specific use or disclosure; (3) if it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to The Container Store, or to others; (4) if we are required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process or governmental request (such as a court order, search warrant, subpoena, civil discovery request, or statutory requirement); or, (5) as we otherwise believe is required by law. 

##  Security of Our Site 

The Container Store maintains security procedures designed to keep information we own, license and process from being accessed by any unauthorized person or business. We use a variety of multi-level security systems to control access to our systems and the data that we house. Our enterprise security operations center maintains real-time monitoring for information system vulnerabilities and unauthorized access attempts into our internal systems. We also maintain physical security for our facilities and limit access to certain critical areas of our business. 

Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to or from our Site, and you do so at your own risk. Accordingly, we disclaim liability for any theft, loss, or interception of, or any unauthorized access or damage to any data or communications. By using our Site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks. 

Anyone with access to the email address and password you use to create an account with us can obtain access to the personal information you have provided to us. We urge you to keep your password in a safe place and not share it with anyone. Always sign out from your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit to our Site. This ensures that others cannot access your account, which is especially important if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place. 

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account password, and you are responsible for any access to or use of our Site by any person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by you. 

##  Reviewing and Revising Your Account Information 

You may review and make changes to the personal information that is stored in your user account on our Site by visiting the "My Account" area of our Site. 

##  Opting Out 

While we hope that the information included in this Privacy Policy has helped you better understand how we use and protect your information to provide you with better service, we understand that you may still choose to not receive information from The Container Store or our partners. 

  * **Direct Mail Opt-Out**. All of our catalogs and direct mailers have information printed on them (generally on the address panel) giving customers notice on how to opt out of our direct mail promotions. To be removed from future mailings from The Container Store, please call us at 1-800-733-3532. After the voice message, please follow the prompts to remove your name from our future mailings. You will be asked for your name, address and customer number as they appear on our mailings. Your request is processed as quickly as possible. Due to mailing lead times however, it is possible that you may receive a few more mailings from us. After six to eight weeks, you should no longer receive mailings from The Container Store. You may also opt out online at www.containerstore.com/preferences   

  * **Email Opt-Out**. All of our marketing emails include a link for unsubscribing to our emails. Registered users on our Site can also log on to the "My Account" section to change their email preferences. We will apply your unsubscribe request as quickly as possible. There may be promotional email campaigns in process and you may continue to receive emails from us for a few days. We require up to ten days to apply your unsubscribe request. After this time, you will no longer receive marketing emails from The Container Store. You may still receive emails regarding your transactions; for example, confirming that you have placed an order, that a product you have ordered has been shipped or a reminder of a pending elfa space design. You may also opt out online at www.containerstore.com/email/frequency.htm

##  Children and Privacy 

Our Site is not directed to children under the age of 13 years. We will never request personally identifiable information from anyone whom we know to be under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. By using our Site, you represent and warrant that you are at least 13 years old. If we become aware that a customer is under the age of 13 and has registered without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable registration information. 

In addition, you must be at least 18 years old in order to establish an online account. By creating an online account with us you represent and warrant that you are at least 18 years of age. 

##  Information Provided When You Apply for a Job Online 

Our Site includes a feature ("Careers") that allows you to submit an online job application. When you submit an online application, you will be required to provide personal information, including but not limited to your name, contact information, job interests, educational and job history, and references. This information will be used by The Container Store to assess and process your application. 

The online application process is hosted and supported by a third-party service provider, HRsmart. HRsmart receives and stores the information you provide. HRsmart does not disclose the personal information it receives and maintains for The Container Store to anyone else. (Click here to see the HRsmart Privacy Policy.) 

If we decide to interview you, we may print your application and use it during the interview process. If you are hired, your application becomes part of your employee file. If you are not immediately hired, your printed application is kept for one year and then typically will be destroyed. We may ask you to provide additional information during the interview or hiring process. We may also use the information you provide to contact you about your application; for example, to ask you to agree to a background check or to send you an offer letter. 

We do not share the information you provide in the online application to anyone outside of The Container Store and HRsmart, except as we believe is required by law. 

##  Questions 

If you need any other information, please submit your requests or questions to The Container Store, ATTN: Customer Solutions Department, 500 Freeport Parkway, Coppell, TX 75019 or email us at [contain@containerstore.com](mailto:contain@containerstore.com) Please allow 30 days for a response. 

##  Please Note 

Our practices relating to sharing personal information changed in June 2014. If you provided personal information to us in June 2014 or earlier, that information will be treated in accordance with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time it was collected by us.
